

Varun R Gupta

Programmer, Web Developer & Designer

52, 11th Main, 30th Cross Banashankari 2nd Stage Bengaluru, INDIA 560070 ▼ WHC9+8C BSK

- **&** +91 97398 56528
- ઢ varungupta3009

Experience



Corporate Operations Engineer II

Google

May 2023 – Present (1 mo)

Corporate Operations Engineer

Jan 2022 - May 2023 (1 yr 5 mos)

IT Resident

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022 (6 mos)

Data and Reporting Analyst Hewlett Packard Enterprise Feb 2021 - Aug 2021 (7 mos)

Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University Jan 2019 – Sep 2020 (1 yr 9 mos)

Software Engineer

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

Education



PES University

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 - 2021



R. V. PU College

K-PUC (CS), Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi



Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka 2002 – 2015

Publications & Awards

Twitter Spam Review Detection Using Hybrid Machine Learning Techniques Springer, November 2021, ISBN: 978-981-16-3690-5

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier

IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

Languages

हिंदी (Hindi) English ಕನ್ನಡ (Kannada)

Hobbies

Reading

Gaming

X	Virtual	Aviation

⁄lusic

Knowledge and Skills

Python 3 Experience Skill	
JavaScript Experience Skill	
C/C++ Experience Skill	

Windows 7/8/10

Experience Skill

Frontend Design and Development

Experience	
Skill	

Full-Stack Web Development

Experience	
Skill	

Angular (TS), React (JS/TS)

Experience	
Skill	
SKIII	

WordPress, CMS

Experience	
Skill	

Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

Experience	
Skill	

Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro

Experience	
zxperrerree	
Skill	
SKIII	

Blender, Pixar Renderman

Experience	
Skill	

Cloud Architechture (GCP)

Experience	
Experience	
Skill	

About me

I am an experienced developer with proficiency in web design. Fluent in many computing languages with over 11 years of experience in Python, C++, and JS. Polymath, geek, and love to explore the bleeding edge of technology and internet. I am also a hobbyist designer and hacker.

Let's Connect

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile to stay regularly updated, and to get in touch with me instantly.

